<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="category_couple_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Couple Sex</field>
            <field name="url">couple_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Couple sex story of husband sex with wife, cumshot in mouth, anal, teen sex on honeymoon, hot wife sex and defloration, licking ass, pissing and bathroom sex, fucking on mouth, cuckold indian wife sex.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_incest_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Incest Sex</field>
            <field name="url">incest_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Incest sex story is a real sex within the family, mom sex with son, aunty sex, mom fucking son, blackmail within family; sex with mother in law, brother in law sex and feel safe.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_virgin_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Virgin Sex</field>
            <field name="url">virgin_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Virgin sex story is a teen losing her virginity, first time sex, masturbate, mouth fucking, lick boobs enjoying pleasure from inside.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_gay_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Gay Sex</field>
            <field name="url">gay_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Gay sex story is a love of male, blowjob to men, fuck in mouth, gay experience in anal, balls licking, old uncle sex with young boy, young boy fucking old.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_group_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Group Sex</field>
            <field name="url">group_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Group sex story is a cock sucking, hard fucking, and loud moans of joy as all holes are filled and big cumshots, threesome sex, foursome sex, enjoy with multiple partners.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_girlfriend_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Girlfriend Sex</field>
            <field name="url">girlfriend_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Girlfriend sex story is a teen sex with classmate, student sex, love sex, cumshot in mouth, girlfriend blackmail and first time sex experience.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_office_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Office Sex</field>
            <field name="url">office_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Office sex story is a sex with a slutty secretaries, doctor cheating with nurse, teacher sex with headmaster, boss sex with milf, sex with beautiful babes in office room.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_family_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Family Sex</field>
            <field name="url">family_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Family sex story is a sex within the house mates, father fucking daughter, son fuck mom, mom illegal relationship with son, sex with mother-in-law, aunty sex with young boy, virgin daughter fucked by father.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_aunty_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Aunty Sex</field>
            <field name="url">aunty_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Indian aunty sex story where aunty gives blowjob, aunty fuck with young boy, young boy fuck big boobs aunty, aged aunty sex, anal sex aunty, aunty mouth fucked, aunty ass fucked, old indian aunty sex with young boy.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_stranger_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Stranger Sex</field>
            <field name="url">stranger_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Casual sex story is sex with strangers, aunty sex with someone unknown, aunty sex on bus travel, aunty sex on rail travel, seduce unsatisfied aunty. cuckold esx, indian cuckold husband sex.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="category_lesbian_sex" model="story.category">
            <field name="name">Lesbian Sex</field>
            <field name="url">lesbian_sex_story</field>
            <field name="description">Lesbian sex story, lesbos, lady love on another lady, fucking with dildo, blowjob, ass licking, pussy licking, tits fucked, girl or teen sex with student, hostel in mates and neighbours, girl licking another girl and fucking with dildo.</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>